Armani Brown

Web Developer

https://armani-tech.netlify.app/ in https://www.linkedin.com/in/armani-brown-14725616b/

https://github.com/ChromeMatic

About Me

Hello, my name is Armani Brown and I am a frontend developer, I am a highly motivated individual who is willing to learn and demonstrate my skills in vue.js, spring boot, and PostgreSQL. I bring four years of experience and a bachelor's degree in Computer Information systems.

Professional Experience

06/2022 – present Kingston, Jamica Web Development Officer

Cok Sodality Co-operative ☑

06/2019 – present New Kingston, St. Andrew

Internship

Aye Technologies Limited ☑

- Refined and finalized designs by closely collaborating with senior engineers on code implementation, validation, and debugging.
- Worked closely with colleagues to implement new features on the frontend using vue.js.
- Worked on implementing features on the backend code comprising of Spring boot.

Education

08/2017 - 08/2022

Bsc Computer Information Systems

Northern Caribbean University 2

Skills

Vue.js

NUXT.JS

SPRING BOOT

DOCKER

React.js

EXPRESS.JS

Git

FIGMA

Languages

lava

Javascript

PHP

Python

C++

Projects

12/2021 - present

ESI ♂

Entech Software Innovations

Entech Software Innovations is a small tech startup located in Jamaica. We specialize in Mobile and app development we're in the current stages of finalizing our website.

Technologies used:

Vue.js, Tailwindcss, Vite

The purpose of this project is to provide a website to track cryptocurrency and get the

latest news on cryptocurrency.

Technologies used: **Vue.js, Tailwindcss, Vite**

03/2020 True Alpha's Pay Day loan ☑

This website offers loans to individuals. Technologies used Vue.js, buetify css

08/2020 – 11/2020 **School Management System (Front end)** ☑

The general goal of this project is to give students and teachers one web application, where students can log in to get their assignments and learning resources for their

classes and get the live class sessions.

Technologies used: Nuxt.js, Vue.js, Tailwind.css, Docker

08/2020 – 11/2020 School Management System (Back-end) ☑

The general goal of this project is to give students and teachers one web application, where students can log in to get their assignments and learning resources for their classes and get live class sessions.

Technologies used: Springboot, SpringJPA, Spring Security, Docker and PostgreSQL